(Amy:)We're looking good.
We are... (giggles)
(Amy:)Better than good.
(Amy:)I mean, look at you.
Your body's bangin'!
Amy!
Don't "Amy" me.
(Amy:)We're always talking
about how hot Penny is.
(Amy:)Come on-- scientist
to scientist,
(Amy:)how big are those
Hadron Colliders?
(Bernadette:)You're embarrassing me.
(Amy:)Oh, don't be embarrassed.
(Amy:)I'll show you the divot
in my spine.
(Amy:)What?
No, no, it's okay.
I was born with it.
(Amy:)If you put a double-A
battery in there,
(Amy:)it makes my leg kick.
(Leonard:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Oh, this is already better.
There are
(Sheldon:)far fewer distractions in here.
(Raj:)Plus, this is where our minds
(Raj:)are conditioned
to focus on work.
(Leonard:)So, I've been thinking
about the hover boards,
(Leonard:)and maybe there's a way
we could use maglev technology.
(Howard:)Or if we could figure out a
way to supercool the materials,
(Howard:)we could utilize
quantum coupling.
(Sheldon:)Well, I wonder
if anyone's tried that.
(Raj:)Go online and look it up.
(Howard:)Oh, I can't argue with him.